Mss.Ms.Coll.137
American Philosophical Society
- III. Works by Mosteller, 1941-2004; 4.5 Linear feet (Box 15-23)
  - Some Evaluation Needs, 1993; 298; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 22)
    Final poof and photocopy of chapter from K. S. Warren and Mosteller (eds.), Doing More Good than Harm: The Evaluation of Health Care Interventions (New York Academy of Sciences, 1993).
  - Some Features of Cumulative Meta-Analysis, 1991; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 22)
  - Some Issues in Health Care Technology Assessment, 1988; Burdick, Elisabeth; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 22)
  - Some Preliminary PGA Tour Analyses, 1991; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006; Youtz, Cleo (Box 22)
  - Some Problems in Determining Maxima of Functions of Several Variables, 1952-1953; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 22)
  - Some Progress and Problems in Meta-Analysis of Clinical Trials, 1990-1992; 278; Chalmers, Thomas C., (Thomas Clark), 1917-1995; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 22)
    Paper delivered at the 2nd International Conference of the Bernouli Society, Uppsala, Sweden, August 14, 1990. Printed in Statistical Science, Vol. 7, No. 2.
  - Some Topics of Interest to Graduate Students in Statistics, 1970; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 22)
  - Stanley Smith Stevens, 1974; 118; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006, et al (Box 22)
  - Statistical Comparisons of Anesthetics: The National Halothane Study, 1967; 78; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 22)
    Bulletin of the International Statistical Institute, Proceedings of the 36th Session
  - Statistical Study of the Writing Styles of the Authors of The Federalist Papers, 1985; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 22)
  - Statistics, 1947-1950; 39a; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 22)
    From Collier's Encyclopedia
  - Statistics, 1974; 114; Hoaglin, David C. (David Caster), 1944-; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 22)
    From the Encylopaedia Britannica, 15th edition
  - Steady Social Progress Requires Quantitative Evaluation in the Searching, 1974-1976; 126; Gilbert, John P.; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006; Tukey, John W., (John Wilder), 1915-2000 (Box 22)
    Two versions: 1. Social Programs Evaluation Conference (1974). 2. From Abt (ed.), The Evaluation of Social Programs
  - Strengthening the Research Environment, 1991; 250; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006, et al (Box 22)
  - Structural and Statistical Problems for a Class of Stochastic Processes, 1971; 91; Cramer, Harald, 1893-1985; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 22)
    Complete copy of Cramer's Structural and Statistical Problems for a Class of Stochastic Processes. Mosteller wrote the introduction.
  - Student Ratings of College Teaching: Review and Recommendations, 1995-1996; 3.0 folders; Emerson, John D.; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006; Youtz, Cleo (Box 22)
    Three manuscript drafts
  - Subject Matter at the Secondary Level, 1973; 113; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 22)
    Page from Howson (ed.), Developments in Mathematical Education
  - Summary, 1987; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 22)
    Manuscript copy of a talk summing up a conference
  - Summary of the Report of the Commission on Mathematics, 1959; College Entrance Examination Board.; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 22)
  - Survival from Localized Breast Cancer - Variability Across Trials and Registries, 1993; 296; Berkey, Catherine S.; Chalmers, Thomas C., (Thomas Clark), 1917-1995; Klawansky, Sidney; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006; Shah, Nirav (Box 22)
    International Journal of Technology Assessment in Health Care, Vol. 9, No. 4. Annotated proof and photocopy.
  - Sustained Inquiry in Education: Lessons from Skill Grouping and Class Size, 1995-1996; 325, 343; Light, Richard J.; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006; Sachs, Jason A. (Box 22)
    Reprint from Harvard Educational Review, Vol. 66, No. 4; list of references not cited; and summary.
  - Tennessee Study of Class Size in the Early School Grades, 1995-1997; 316, 330, 340; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 23)
    The Future of Children, Vol. 5, No. 2.
    Bulletin, The American Academy of Arts and Sciences, Vol. L, No. 7.
    Brillinger et al (eds.), The Practice of Data Analysis: Essays in Honor of John W. Tukey
  - Tentative Recommendations for the Undergraduate Mathematics Program of Students in the Biological, Management, and Social Sciences, 1964; Committee on the Undergraduate Program in Mathematics. (Box 23)
    First draft. Mosteller served on the committee.
  - Tenth Annual Report of the Department of Statistics, 1966-1967; Harvard University. Department of Statistics.; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 23)
  - Testimony of Frederick Mosteller Regarding the Radioepidemiologic Tables, 1985; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006; Saenger, Eugene L.; Senate Committee on Labor and Human Resources. (Box 23)
    Includes work by Saenger, "Possible Medical Consequences Arising from the Use of the Radioepidemiological Tables"
  - Three Programs for Medical Education of Underrepresented Minorities, 2000-2001; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006; Youtz, Cleo (Box 23)
  - Toward an Integrated Assessment of the Efficacy and Safety of Medical Technologies, 1983-1984; 3.0 folders; Bailar, John C., (John Christian), 1904-1991; Fineberg, Harvey V.; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 23)
    Includes notes, drafts, correspondence regarding funding
  - Toward Evaluating the Cost-Effectiveness of Medical and Social Experiments, 1981-1985; 194; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006; Weinstein, Milton C. (Box 23)
    From Hausman and Wise (eds.), Social Experimentation.
    National Bureau of Economic Research, Conference Paper Series, No. 124.
  - Tribute to Walter Shewhart, 1967; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 23)
    Industrial Quality Control, Vol. 24, No. 2
  - Two-Way Order Statistics, 1970; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006; Weisberg, Harvey S. (Box 23)
  - Uncertainty of the First Instance of Significance in Random-effects Cumulative Meta-analysis, 1995; Antman, Elliott M.; Berkey, Catherine S.; Lau, Joseph; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 23)
  - Understanding Research Synthesis (Meta-Analysis), 1995-1996; 320; Colditz, Graham A.; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 23)
    Annotated proof and reprint from Annual Review of Public Health (1996), Vol. 17
  - Unemployed Field Trial and Other Research Designs: Findings from a Survey of Education Research in the 1990s, 1998-1999; Miech, Edward J.; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006; Nave, Bill (Box 23)
    Manuscript, notes, and correspondence.
  - Using Controlled Field Studies to Improve Public Policy, 1971; 93; Light, Richard J.; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006; Winokur, Herbert S. (Box 23)
    From Report of the President's Commission, Federal Statistics, Vol. II
  - Vitamin A Supplementation and Child Mortality - A Meta-Analysis, 1993; 285; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006, et al (Box 23)
    Annotated review from JAMA, Vol. 269, No. 7
  - Where Eagles Fly, 1993; 289; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006; Youtz, Cleo (Box 23)
    Chance, Vol. 6, No. 2
  - Why We Need a Structured Abstract in Education Research, 2003; Miech, Edward J.; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006; Nave, Bill (Box 23)
    Manuscript drafts
  - William Gemmell Cochran, 1909-1980, 1981-1987; 169, 181, 213; Hansen, Morris H., (Morris Howard), 1910-1990; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 23)
    American Statistician, Vol. 35, No.1.
    Harvard University Gazette, Vol. 78, No. 14.
    National Academy of Sciences. Reprinted from Biographical Memoirs, Vol. 56.
  - Workshop on the Future of Meta-Analysis: Summary Remarks, 1986; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 23)
  - World Series Competition, 1952-1953; 25; Mosteller, Frederick, 1916-2006 (Box 23)
    Reprint in English from Journal of the American Statistical Association, vol. 47; and in French from Hermes, vol. 8
- IV. Works by Others, 1934-2005; 3.0 Linear feet (Box 24-29)
  - Small Group and Individual Learning with Technology: A Meta-Analysis, 2001; Abrami, Philip C.; D'Apollonia, Sylvia; Lou, Yiping (Box 24)
    Annotated copy of reprint from Review of Educational Research, Vol. 71, No. 3
  - Popular Critical View of the Isaiah Problem in Light of Statistical Style Analysis, n.d.; Adams, L. La Mar; Rencher, Alvin C., 1934- (Box 24)
  - Ambulatory Cardiac Monitoring for the Evaluation of Antiarrhythmic Agents, 1992; Adams, Miriam E.; Antczak-Bouckoms, Alexia Anne; Tulloch, J. F. C. (Box 24)
  - Noninvasive Testing of Asymptomatic Post-Infarction Patients for the Detection of Silent Ischemia: A Decision Analysis, 1992; Adams, Miriam E.; Lau, Joseph (Box 24)
  - Dropout 2000, Alexander, Karl L.; Entwisle, Doris R.; Olson, Linda Steffel (Box 24)
    See also Series I, Correspondence, John Emerson
  - First Grade and Educational Attainment by Age 22, 2003; Alexander, Karl L.; Entwisle, Doris R.; Olson, Linda Steffel (Box 24)
  - Statistics and Politics: The Need for Causal Data Analysis, 1967; Alker, Hayward R. (Box 24)
  - Statistics in Medical Papers, 1977; Altman, Douglas G. (Box 24)
    Journal of the Royal College of Physicians, Vol. 11, No. 3
  - Conference on Evaluation of Educational Policies, 1999; 8.0 folders; American Academy of Arts and Sciences. (Box 24)
    - Conference on Evaluation of Educational Policies, 1999; American Academy of Arts and Sciences. (Box 24)
    - Educational Resources, Instruction, and Research, 1999; American Academy of Arts and Sciences.; Ball, Deborah Loewenberg, 1954-; Cohen, David K., 1934-; Raudenbush, Stephen W. (Box 24)
    - Importance of Randomized Field Trials, 1999-2000; American Academy of Arts and Sciences.; Boruch, Robert F.; DeMoya, Dorothy; Snyder, Brooke (Box 24)
    - What to Evaluate to Improve Learning, 1999; American Academy of Arts and Sciences.; Cole, Nancy S. (Box 24)
    - Considering the Major Arguments against Random Assignment: An Analysis of the Intellectual Culture Surrounding Evaluation in American Schools of Education, 1999; American Academy of Arts and Sciences.; Cook, Thomas D. (Box 24)
    - Politics of Random Assignment: Implementing Studies and Impacting Policy, 1999; American Academy of Arts and Sciences.; Gueron, Judith M. (Box 24)
    - Missing in Practice? Systematic Development and Rigorous Program Evaluation at the U.S. Department of Education, 1999; American Academy of Arts and Sciences.; Vinovskis, Maris (Box 24)
    - What to Do Until the Random Assigner Comes, 1999; American Academy of Arts and Sciences.; Weiss, Carol H. (Box 24)
  - Synthesis: Telecourse on Science, Technology, and Society, 1985; American Association for the Advancement of Science; Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers.; WGBH. (Television station: Boston, Mass.) (Box 24)
  - Apparent Anomalies and Irregularities in Maximum Likelihood Estimation, 1961 (Box 24)
    Discussions on paper by C. R. Rao at the 32nd Session of the International Statistical Institute held in Tokyo, June 8, 1960. Annotated reprint from Bulletin of the International Statistical Institute, Vol. 38, No. 1
  - Statistics, Science, and Public Policy: Recommendations for Government and the Scientific Community, 2004; Bailar, John C., (John Christian), 1904-1991; et al (Box 24)
  - Authorship Attribution in a Forensic Setting, 1979; Bailey, Richard W. (Box 24)
    From Ager et al (eds.), Advances in Computer-Aided Literary and Linguistic Research
  - Health Care and Cost Benefit-Analysis: An Application to Intensive Care, 1978; Barnes, Benjamin A., b. 1919 (Box 24)
  - Practical Bayesian Statistics, 1982; Barr, D. R. (Box 24)
    European Scientific Notes, Vol. 36, No. 9
  - Study of Run Production Estimators for Major League Baseball, 1979; Bennett, Jay; Flueck, John A. (Box 24)
  - Clinical Trials, 1975; Bennett, P. N.; Dollery, Colin T. (Box 24)
    British Journal of Clinical Pharmacology, Vol. 2
  - Cancer Incidence and Mortality: The Priority of Screening Frequency and Population Coverage, 1997; Berkey, Catherine S.; Colditz, Graham A.; Hoaglin, David C. (David Caster), 1944- (Box 24)
  - Probability of a Field Goal: Rating Kickers, 1984; Berry, Donald A.; Berry, Timothy D. (Box 24)
  - Variability and Biases of Infant Mortality Rates, 1985; Birnbaum, Z. W., (Zygmund William), 1903-2000; Sirken, Monroe G. (Box 24)
    Statistical Theory and Data Analysis, 1985
  - RA Fisher, Statistician and Geneticist Extraordinary: A Personal View, 2003; Bodmer, Walter (Box 24)
  - Cooperative Learning in the Secondary Mathematics Classroom, 1997; Bol, Linda; Nunnery, John A.; Whicker, Kristina M. (Box 24)
    Annotated reprint from Journal of Educational Research, Vol. 91, No. 1
  - Definitions, Products, and Distinctions in Data Sharing, 1985; Boruch, Robert F. (Box 24)
    From Fienberg et al (eds.), Sharing Research Data
  - Evaluation Techniques: Improvements, and Suggestions for Further Improvement, 1984; Boruch, Robert F. (Box 24)
    From Boruch (ed.), Project Evaluation: Problems of Methodology
  - Golf, January Stats, 1981; Boswell, Thomas, 1948- (Box 24)
    Annotated proof for Golf Digest
  - Bayesian Approaches to Some Bothersome Problems in Data Analysis, 1965; Box, George E. P. (Box 25)
  - Sampling and Bayes' Inference in Scientific Modeling and Robustness, 1980; Box, George E. P. (Box 25)
  - Bayesian Estimation of Common Parameters from Several Responses, 1964; Box, George E. P.; Draper, Norman Richard (Box 25)
  - Multiparameter Problems from a Bayesian Point of View, 1965; Box, George E. P.; Tiao, George C., 1933- (Box 25)
  - Computer in Statistical Studies of William Shakespeare, n.d.; Brainerd, Barron, 1928- (Box 25)
  - Effect of Admissions Test Preparation: Evidence from NELS:88, 2001; Briggs, Derek C. (Box 25)
    Annotated reprint from Chance, Vol. 14, No. 1
  - Analysis of Variance and Problems under Time Series Models, 1980; Brillinger, David R. (Box 25)
    From Krishnaiah (ed.), Handbook of Statistics, Vol. 1
  - Kansas City Preventive Patrol Experiment: A Summary Report, 1974; Brown, Charles E.; Dieckman, Duane; Kelling, George L.; Pate, Tony (Box 25)
  - Decisions Based on Numerically and Verbally Expressed Uncertainties, 1986; Budescu, David V.; Wallsten, Thomas S.; Weinberg, Shalva (Box 25)
    Institute of Information Processing and Decision Making, Report No. 39
  - Six Randomized Experiments on the Effects of Integration on Handicapped and Nonhandicapped Preschoolers, 1999; Buehler, John H. (Box 25)
  - Scared Straight and Other Juvenile Awareness Programs for Preventing Juvenile Delinquency, 2002; Buehler, John H.; Petrosino, Anthony J.; Turpin-Petrosino, Carolyn, 1952- (Box 25)
  - Role of Medical Care in Improving the Quality of Life: An Inventory of Benefits from Secondary Sources, 1995; Bunker, John P. (Box 25)
    From Guggenmoos-Holzmann et al (eds.), Quality of Life and Health: Concepts, Methods, and Applications
  - Meta-Analysis and Program Evaluation: Spanish Studies, 2000; Chacon-Moscoso, Salvador; Marin-Martinez, Fulgenico; Perez-Gil, Jose; Sanchez-Meca, Julio (Box 25)
  - Brief History of Research Synthesis, 2001-2002; Chalmers, Iain; Cooper, Harris; Hedges, Larry V. (Box 25)
    Notes, draft and reprint from Evaluation and the Health Professions, Vol. 25, no. 1
  - Quality Assessment and Meta-Analysis of Randomized Control Trials in Three Areas of Perinatal Research: Prevention of Prematurity, Prevention of Intraventricular Hemorrhage, and Treatment of Hyperbilirubinemia, 1985; Chalmers, Thomas C., (Thomas Clark), 1917-1995 (Box 25)
  - Method for Assessing the Quality of an RCT, 1979; Chalmers, Thomas C., (Thomas Clark), 1917-1995; et al (Box 25)
  - History of Mathematics at Princeton, 1958; Chaplin, Virginia (Box 25)
    Princeton Alumni Weekly, 9 May 1958
  - Sequential Medical Trials with Ethical Cost, 1983; Chernoff, Herman; Petkau, A. John (Box 25)
  - Moments of Some Rank Order Measures of Correlation (Preliminary Report), n.d.; Chow, B.; Dick, W. J. (Box 25)
  - Making the Most of Summer School, 1999; Cooper, Harris; et al (Box 25)
  - Small Group Instruction in Science, Mathematics, Engineering, and Technology, 1998; Cooper, James; Robinson, Pamela, 1942- (Box 25)
    Annotated reprint from Journal of Computer Science and Technology, May 1998
  - Statistical Power of Research in Social and Abnormal Psychology: What Have We Gained in 20 Years?, 1984; Cottrill, Sarah D.; Rossi, Joseph S.; Rossi, Susan R. (Box 25)
  - Grammatical Evidence of Multiple Authorship in Piers Plowman, n.d.; Covella, Francis D. (Box 25)
  - Principal Requirements for Controlled Clinical Trials in Periodontal Diseases, 1977; Davies, G. N., (George Neville); Emslie, Ronald, (Ronald Douglas), 1915-2002 (Box 25)
    International Dental Journal, Vol. 27, No. 1
  - Combining Evidence in Clinical Trials, 1985; DerSimonian, Rebecca; Laird, Nan M., 1943- (Box 25)
  - Curriculum Vitae, 2002; Diaconis, Persi (Box 25)
  - Beliefs about Beliefs, 1980; Dickey, James M.; Good, Irving John (Box 25)
    Two chapters from Bernardo et al (eds.), Bayesian Statistics.
    Dickey, "Beliefs about Beliefs, A Theory of Stochastic Assessments of Subjective Probabilities."
    Good, "Some History of the Hierarchical Bayesian Methodology."
  - Bayesian Methods for Multinomial Sampling with Missing Data Using Multiple Hypergeometric Functions, 1983; Dickey, James M.; Jiang, Jyh-Ming; Kadane, Joseph B. (Box 25)
  - Effects of Small-Group Learning on Undergraduates in Science, Mathematics, Engineering, and Technology: A Meta-Analysis, 1999; Donovan, Samuel S.; Springer, Leonard; Stanne, Mary Elizabeth (Box 25)
    Annotated copy of reprint from Review of Educational Research, Vol. 69, No. 1
  - Bayesian Model and a Graphical Elicitation Procedure for Multiple Comparisons, 1987; DuMouchel, William H. (Box 25)
  - Hierarchical Bayes Linear Models for Meta-Analysis, 1994; DuMouchel, William H. (Box 25)
  - How to Perform a Bayesian Meta-Analysis, 1987; DuMouchel, William H. (Box 25)
  - Bayesian Methodology for Scaling Radiation Studies for Animals to Man, n.d.; DuMouchel, William H.; Groer, Peter G. (Box 25)
  - Bayes and Empirical Bayes Methods for Combining Cancer Experiments in Man and Other Species, 1981; DuMouchel, William H.; Harris, Jeffrey E. (Box 25)
  - Review of Proposal for a National Data Center, 1965; Dunn, Edgar Streeter (Box 25)
  - Home Field Advantage, 1977; Edwards, John (Box 26)
  - Empirical Bayes Methods for Combining Likelihoods, 1994; Efron, Bradley (Box 26)
  - Data Analysis Using Stein's Estimator and its Generalizations, 1974; Efron, Bradley; Morris, Carl N. (Box 26)
  - Design for a Mechanical Distribution Analysis of English Word Classes, 1963; Ellegard, Alvar (Box 26)
    From Ellegard, Karlgren, and Spang-Hanssen, Structures and Quanta
  - Assessing Outcomes for Intercollegiate Athletes at Liberal Arts Colleges, 2004; Emerson, John D. (Box 26)
  - Bayesian Analysis of Multilevel Contingency Tables, 1966; Evans, Robert; Kunz, John; Tribus, Myron (Box 26)
  - Runaways: A Review of the Literature and Policy Recommendations, 1998; Falotico-Taylor, Jennifer (Box 26)
  - On Measuring Economic Benefits of Health Programmes, 1971; Fein, Rashi (Box 26)
    From Medical History and Medical Care
  - On the Theory of Screening for Chronic Diseases, 1969; Feinleib, Manning, 1935-; Zelen, Marvin (Box 26)
  - Current Burden of Illness in the United States, 1977; Feldman, Jacob J.; Rice, Dorothy P.; White, Kerr L. (Box 26)
  - Graphical Methods in Statistics: Current and Prospective Views, 1987; Fisher, N. I. (Box 26)
    Invited Paper 16.3, 46th Session of the ISI
  - Statistical Inference and the Testing of Hypotheses, 1936; Fisher, R. A. (Box 26)
  - Some Episodes in the Life and Times of Division in Extreme and Mean Ratio, 1998; Fowler, David (Box 26)
    From Giusti (ed.), Luca Pacioli e la matematica del rinascimento: Atti del convegno internazionale di studi, Sansepolcro, 13-16 Aprile 1994
  - Diagnosis of Syncope in the Elderly, n.d.; Frazier, Howard S. (Box 26)
  - Aggression and Sport, 1977; Gaskell, George; Pearton, Robert E., 1940- (Box 26)
  - Tables of Power of Conditional Tests for Testing for Equality of Two Proportions, 1976; Gasko-Green, Miriam (Box 26)
  - Bayesian Model Checking Using Tail Area Probabilities, 1993; Gelman, Andrew; Meng, Xiao-Li; Stern, Hal Steven (Box 26)
  - Hot Hand in Basketball: On the Misperception of Random Sequences, 1985; Gilovich, Thomas; Tversky, Amos; Vallone, Robert (Box 26)
    Annotated reprint from Cognitive Psychology, Vol. 17
  - Biostatistics: How to Detect, Correct, and Prevent Errors in the Medical Literature, Glantz, Stanton A. (Box 26)
  - Best Choice from the Planar Poisson Process, 2002; Gnedin, A. V., (Aleksandr Vasil'evich) (Box 26)
  - On Disputed Authorship of Editorials in Kesari, 1979; Gokhale, M. K.; Gore, A. P.; Joshi, S. B. (Box 26)
    Indian Linguistics, Vol. 40
  - On the Statistical Determination of Authorship, 1981; Good, Irving John (Box 26)
    Journal of Statistical Computation and Simulation, Vol. 14, No. 1
  - Relevant Variables in Professional Football, 1977; Goode, Bud (Box 26)
  - New Methods for Analyzing the Intrinsic Character of Qualitative Variables Using Cross-Classified Data, 1985; Goodman, Leo A (Box 26)
  - Computational Probability, 1968; Grenander, Ulf (Box 26)
  - Selection and Ranking Procedures and Order Statistics from the Multinomial Distribution, 1966; Gupta, Shanti Swarup, 1925-; Nagel, Klaus (Box 26)
  - Use of the Concept of a Future Observation in Goodness of Fit Problems, 1965; Guttman, Irwin (Box 26)
  - Modeling Interlaboratory Differences: A Bayesian Analysis, 1989; Guttman, Irwin; Olkin, Ingram (Box 26)
  - Note on the Inverted Multivariate Beta Distribution with Applications, 1964; Guttman, Irwin; Tiao, George C., 1933- (Box 26)
  - Many New Directions of Educational Evaluation, 2000; Hacsi, Timothy A. (Box 26)
  - Note on the Small Groups Adjustment Procedure in the Mosteller Tukey Paull-2 Estimator for the Grand Mean of Several Independent Group Means, 1985; Halvorsen, Katherine Taylor (Box 26)
  - Data Analysis and Self-Similar Processes, 1987; Hampel, Frank R., 1941- (Box 26)
    Invited Paper 25.3, 46th Session of the ISI
  - Harvard College Observatory Solar Project, 1970 (Box 26)
    Harvard Computing Center Newsletter, No. 70-04
  - Football Ratings and Predictions via Linear Models, Harville, David A. (Box 27)
  - Predictions for National Football League Games via Linear-Model Methodology, 1977; Harville, David A. (Box 27)
  - Evaluating Selection Bias for Dichotomous Response Data, 1998; Hauck, Walter W.; Marcus, Susan M.; Newschaffer, Craig J.; Turner, Barbara J., (Barbara Jean), 1950- (Box 27)
  - Battle Royal: Psychology and the Chessplayer, 1977; Hearst, Eliot, 1932-; Wierzbicki, Michael (Box 27)
  - Bayesian Data Analysis, 1988; Hill, Bruce M. (Box 27)
  - Posterior Distribution of Percentiles of a Future Sample, 1966; Hill, Bruce M. (Box 27)
  - Posterior Distribution of the Mean of a Future Sample, 1966; Hill, Bruce M. (Box 27)
  - Theory of Bayesian Data Analysis, 1988; Hill, Bruce M. (Box 27)
  - Social and Economic Implications of Cancer in the United States, 1978; Hodgson, Thomas A.; Rice, Dorothy P. (Box 27)
  - What Certainty Can There Be on How Much Treatments Work: Empirical Insight from Recursive Cumulative Meta-Analyses, 2000; Ioannidis, John P.; Lau, Joseph (Box 27)
  - Robust Analysis of Factorial Designs via Elemental Subsets and Outlier Sterilization, 1989; Johnson, Eugene G. (Box 27)
  - Positional Models and Empty Positions, 1963; Karlgren, Hans, 1933- (Box 27)
  - Career Academies: Impacts on Students' Engagement and Performance in High School, 2000; Kemple, James J. (Box 27)
  - Aristotle's Theory of the Will, 1979; Kenny, Anthony, 1931- (Box 27)
  - Classroom Management, Teacher Training, and Student Engagement/Achievement, 2001; Kim, James S. (Box 27)